MOK CHI HONG

FULL STACK WEB & MOBILE DEVELOPER

CONTACT +6016-420 7769 mokchi2324@hotmail.com https://joseph-portfolio-ugu2y6salaas.a.run.app/ https://www.linkedin.com/in/chi-hong98/ SKILLS

Flutter Git

Laravel TypeScript

RESTful API ReactJs

Yii2 YOLOv5

PHP **GCP**

MySQL JavaScript

Tailwind CSS Docker

EDUCATION

University of Greenwich

Bachelor Of Science (HONS) Computing

2019 - 2021 | 3.91 CGPA

- · First class honours
- · Best student award

SEGi College Penang

Diploma In Information Technology

2016 - 2018 | 3.62 CGPA

- Vice president of Multi-Tech Society
- Champion of SEGi Video Competition

LANGUAGES

English	
Chinese	
Malay	

PROFILE

Full stack developer with 3 years of working experience in both mobile and web development. My proficient is in developing full stack web application using Laravel / Yii2 Framework, mobile application with Flutter and backend RESTful APIs. I specialized in creating user-friendly applications by writing clean, reusable and maintainable code. I'm passionate about staying updated with latest trend in web and mobile development. Currently seeking job opportunity in related field. I have experience leading a team and also capable of working with minimal supervision. I love to accept new challenges and I'm a fast learner.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead Software Engineer

Silkron Technology Sdn Bhd

Jan 2023 - Present

- Lead and manage team of engineers by providing guidance and mentorship.
- Develop and maintain a cross platform mobile application for both Android and IOS devices using Flutter framework.
- Deploy and maintain mobile application on both Google play and Apple app
- Develop and integrate RESTful APIs into mobile application.
- Continuously optimize app and API performance to enhance user satisfaction and overall efficiency
- · Code base version control with GIT and SVN

Software Engineer

Silkron Technology Sdn Bhd

June 2021 - Jan 2023

- Design, implement and manage web application with Yii2 Framework and JS
- Develop and maintain WeChat Mini program.
- Al Model training with YOLOv5 object detection algorithm and image labeling using PaddleSeg.
- Develop and maintain mobile application on both Google Play and Apple app
- Develop and integrate RESTful APIs into mobile application and WeChat App.
- · Code base version control with SVN

Intern

Silkron Technology Sdn Bhd

Jan 2021 - June 2021

- Design, develop and maintain web-based solution with MySQL, JS and Yii2 PHP
- Assist senior debug and solve web related problems.

Intern

Zepheus Corporate Services Sdn Bhd

June 2020 - Sept 2020

 Design and develop responsive web-base secretary system using MySQL, JS, Jguery and Laravel PHP Framework.